Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Performances and Exhibitions, 1960-2013; 82.4 Linear Feet in 44 cassette boxes, 33 record cartons, 12 manuscript boxes, 5 LP boxes, 5 flat files, and 4 flat boxes; 665 audiocassettes; 202 Hi8; 170 VHS; 137 MiniDV; 78 U-matic; 58 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 29 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4 Betamax
  - Subseries I.C: Events by Date, 1967-2013
    - Greek music, Greek alphabet, circa 1975-1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0431)
    - Lyrics, melody, vocals, circa 1975-1978 (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0472)
    - Piano rehearsal and performance, Museum of Modern Art, circa 1975-1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0411)
    - Riis Park Sculpture, circa 1975-1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0471)
      Full label reads: "Riis Park - sun, blank start - morning, beach words + under the sculpture, July 22, Riis Park snow, reactions to sculpture"
    - Talk with Carol at her Studio, drums practice at the State Fair, circa 1975-1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0436)
    - Water Harp by Arleen Schloss, circa 1975-1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0425)
    - Water Harp by Ray Kelly, circa 1975-1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0442)
    - Compilation Tape -- Cage theater piece, Rapp Art Center, Alfresco's 75th birthday, Lincoln Center, Songbooks, 1960-1988 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1035)
    - Collage of event ephemera, circa 1975 - 1985 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Compilation of early works, circa 1975-1985; FA_MSS_437_ER_1
    - "Words and Elastics" Show, Betty Parsons Gallery, February 8-26, 1976 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0844)
    - SDRAWKSCAB, March, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0825)
    - Betty Parsons Gallery, March 21, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0813)
    - "Frontwards and Backwards", April 8, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0819)
    - Evening of Poetry, May 12, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Poetry event, Betty Bush Skye Vermont, May 12, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0824)
    - ABC -- Kid Come Back, John and Danny, Skye, July, 1976 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0843)
    - Cigarette, September 8, 1976 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0392)
      Featuring John Smead - guitar, vocals; Danny Wallack - bass; Bob Dakin - flute, sax; Judy Steig - vocals; Dave Span - drums; Miguel Roserio - congas
    - Vocal Text Performance, Construction Company, October, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Generations" Xerox Exhibit, Popular Photography, October 1 - 29, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Soho Center for Visual Artists Exhibition, November - December, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alphabets and Languages, Greece, 1976; cuid44183
      - Audio recording, cuid44141 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2426)
        This item was isolated for visible mold in 2025.
      - National Recording Studios Log (Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 12)
    - Alphabets and Languages, Subway, Interview, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0823)
    - Layered Tape, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0821)
    - Reading Dylan Thomas, Typewriter, Ramone rehearsal, 1976 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0846)
      Full label reads: "Reading Dylan Thomas 'If I Were Tickled by the Rub of Love,' 'A Winter's Tale,' 'Poem on His Birthday,' 'There Was a Saviour'; Typewriter + Ramone rehearsal"
    - Soho Performance, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "Spiral", 1976
      - Part one (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0822)
      - Part two (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0812)
    - Typewriter 1 and 2, 1976 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0820)
    - American bandstand, string rehearsal, ABC, sounds, February 4, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0914)
    - David Allen Coe concert, taped by Arleen, February 12, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0913)
    - Layered tape, March, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0921)
    - Hedda's performance, March 10, 1977 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0909)
    - A and Do Do, Penny, March 18, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0911)
    - Layers with Katy, April, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0908)
    - Stereo, Rhythm at S. Again's roof, April 30, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0917)
    - Performance at Braathan and Friedus, Hedda's at East Hampton, July, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0907)
    - Arleen, Lynn, and Claire musical performance, July 4, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0912)
    - Compilation Tape -- Voice as Instrument, A Shot Chance, October 5-12, 1977
      - Video (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_2418)
        Full label reads: "Part 1 - 10 min, performed by Arleen Schloss, Voice as Instrument, presented on Paul Tschinkel's Inner Tube-Cable, NYC; Part 2 - 20 min, performed by Arleen Schloss, A Shot Chance, presented at The Kitchen Center for Video and Music, 484 Broome St. NYC"
      - Video (Box 119, U-matic 437_1112)
        Full label reads: "Alphabets," Paul Tschinkel's Inner Tube-Cable, A Shot Chance, The Kitchen"
    - Rehearsal and performance, November 30 - December 17, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0910)
      Label also reads: "Rehearsal 1st half, Lynn, Ingrid, Alise and Arleen; Performance #1 NYC"
    - Museum of Modern Art, Vienna, 1975-1979 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0466)
      Full label reads: "Side A: In Museum of Modern Art, Vienna 1979 - Looking at painting, general idea show, Modern Art Gas. - Evening / Side B: Some A's B+F, Biennal Talk, Biennal - at park - talking - band - me whistling a little - Aperque - sounds"
    - "Words," Tomiyo Sasaki, Ernest Gusella, 1976-1977 (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1945)
    - "Tapsnap" Performance, Hedda's, March 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "Arleen Schloss at Midnight," Galerie Do-Do, March 18, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "Rhythm" Performance, Betty Parsons Gallery, April 20, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "O.E" Performance, November 30, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Ernie and Tom, December 30, 1977 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0439)
    - Alphabet, 1977
      - Group and waterharp (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0398)
      - Layered alphabet (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0397)
      - Layered tape, sound experiments, rehearsal (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0915)
      - Layers end, short and long vowels (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0400)
    - Drum and voice, Hedda, East Hampton, 1977 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0905)
    - N Do Do band, 1977 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0328)
    - Rehearsal for BP Rhythm, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0916)
    - "Shot" Performance, Walden School, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - To Hedda's, from Hedda's, 1977 (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0946)
    - Waterharp by Ray Kelly, John Smead, 1977 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0402)
    - Shot Dot Shot, 1977-1979
      - Original performance at the Kitchen, 1977 (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1941)
      - London, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Robert Frick's, circa 1979 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1470)
      - Audio, October, 1979 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0388)
      - Audio, October 31, 1979 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0175)
        Performance also includes Bottles
      - Audio, October 31, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0624)
      - Audio, October 31, 1979 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0404)
        Performance also includes an intro by Eva and Maureen, Bottles, Alphabets, and "Tu as des Beaux Yeux"
      - Audio, November 27, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0608)
    - Alphabet, Katy, circa 1977-1978 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0405)
    - A Shot Chance Performances, 1977-1980; cuid44146
      - Original, circa 1977 (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1940)
      - The Kitchen, October 2, 1977 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0920)
      - The Kitchen, October 11, 1977; cuid44147 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0395)
      - The Kitchen, October 11, 1977; cuid44139 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0010)
        Annotation reads, "RHYTHM | [AS HOT HANDLE] | DUB OF DOUB | DROPOUT | EDIT STILL NEEDED (NEAR END)"
      - Café Einstein, Berlin, 1980 (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1955)
    - Compilation Tape -- Performance and Film Works, 1977-1980 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2146)
      Full label reads: "Freidus -- A edit; Kids; Sleep; Golf Balls -- 16mm; "Wallband" edited; Shot Dot; A shots - DTW, 1977; SNAFU, 1980; Performance Art Workshop; How She Sees It By Her; Subway footage; Armageddon; Laser / instant burn water; P.S. 185; Penny"
    - Compilation Tape -- Recite Alphabets, Paul Tschida / Inner Tube, Shot Dot Shot, Freidus Gallery, MoMA, Düsseldorf, Bubbling at A's, Monster Mash 81, How She Sees It, X-35, 1977-1981 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2147)
    - Performance Compilation -- "Shot Dot," MoMA, Etc., 1977-1982; FA_MSS_437_ER_2
    - For Offenur Kanal, 1977-1991 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1029)
    - "Its 7up" Performances, Musawwir Gymnastic Dance Company, January, 1978
      - Rehearsal, January 8-11, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0816)
      - Ephemera, January 12, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Audio, January 12-15, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0441)
      - Video, January 14, 1978 (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_2419)
      - Audio, January 14-15, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0446)
      - Ephemera, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36, Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Betty Parsons Gallery Performance, January 3, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0455)
    - Pearl's Place, January 27, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0406)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sounds on sound, rhythm box, "Words and Setters," story with B. Jerry, February - March, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0451)
    - Ernie Kovacs Excerpts, March, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0419)
    - Rhys Chatham at Franklin Furnace, March 14, 1978; cuid44118 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0416)
      Duration: 63 minutes
      Also includes Delbert McClinton-Lonestar and John Talley.
    - Performance, Robert Freidus Gallery, April, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0453)
    - Sukanya Indrani and grandmother, Asia House Concert, April 5, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0413)
    - Arleen Schloss and the Alphabetts, Robert Freidus Gallery, April 12, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - Rhythm box performance, April 12, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0815)
    - Compilation Tape -- World Trade Center Performance, "AAA" edited version, Arlene Krebs prison tape, April 23-28, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0432)
    - Exercise -- Antler Gianakis, April 27, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0418)
    - Meeting with Veronica Fomio's writings, R. Morrow, Bogril, May - July, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0459)
    - Brooklyn Museum, May 3, 1978 (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0474)
    - Compilation Tape -- Ernie Kovacs, Hebrew alphabet, "It's A", May 3, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0427)
    - Rhythm Box Performance, Ear Inn, May 12, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0810)
    - "Galvanized Voice" -- Richard Hepner, Yoshi, John Lee Hooker at Lonestar, May 13-17, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0444)
    - Night Club, Sauvagion, May 20, 1978; cuid44152 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0006)
    - "In the Water", May 25, 1978; cuid44153
      - Beginning of Procession, cuid44154 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0002)
      - The Procession, cuid44155 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0005)
    - Claire Fergusson and Arleen Schloss at Franklin Furnace, May 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Compilation Tape -- Phoebe's UN Talk, Performance at Franklin Furnace, Arleen and Claire, May 30 - June, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0805)
    - A at B, June, 1978; cuid44160 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0014)
    - A on drums, June, 1978 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0918)
    - Compilation Tape -- Jammin' with Lindsay, Phil Glass at Carnegie Hall, June, 1978 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0884)
    - Keri, Arleen, and Jon Performance, June 2 - July 3, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0452)
    - Charlie Morrow - Composition Solstice at Central Park, June 21, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0420)
      Recorded by Arleen Schloss
    - Sullivan County Concert, July 1, 1978 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0422)
    - Uptown subway to Modern, Out at David's House, July 25, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0438)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Uptown subway to Modern + street / Side B: Out at David Bernhart's (?) house in Rye, NY with Ray and (illegible)"
    - Compilation Tape -- Gallery and Richard, Kat, German Alphabet, Yonkers Words, July, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0429)
    - Barn Performances, July - August, 1978
      - Piano, July 31, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0434)
      - Piano, alphabet, words, reactions, August 16, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0430)
      - Piano, trowel, saw, tack with Laura, August 17, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0454)
    - Cleaning sand and piano, lunch, August 2, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0435)
    - Piano, new studio, August 12, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0808)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Mostly great piano / Side B: New studio and piano (illegible), Bria"
    - "Performance Art at Skowhegan" Event, August 16, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Museum of Modern Art Meetings, August 28 - September 11, 1978
      - #1 Daniel Lee, Jacki Apple, August 28, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0433)
      - Meeting with Cee Brown, Arlene Krebs on Subway, Meeting with Daniel Lee, August 30, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0458)
      - #2, Words, Cee Brown, Kim Halsey, John Smead, August 30 - September 11, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0426)
    - German letters -- Michael Kohler, September 3, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0449)
    - Piano warmup and performance, the Ear Inn, September 7, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0409)
    - "Mirrors and Windows" piano rehearsal, September 12-13, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0450)
    - Piano performance, Museum of Modern Art, September 22, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0456)
    - Piano and vocals, Museum of Modern Art, September 26, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0414)
    - Word rehearsals and piano, Museum of Modern Art, September - October, 1978 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0847)
    - "It's A at MoMA" Performance, October 13, 1978; cuid44142
      - Audio, cuid44144 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2431)
      - Audio, cuid44145 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2432)
      - Audio, cuid44143 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2425)
      - Composite performance data with segues (Box 119, U-matic 437_1113)
      - Ephemera and posters (Box 1, Folder 26, Box 62, Folder 2)
      - New Wilderness Foundation Log (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 10)
      - Video (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0031)
      - Video (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0032)
      - Video (Box 120, Vhs 437_1191)
      - Video (Box 126, U-matic 437_1496)
      - Video (Box 124, U-matic 437_1563)
        Recorded by Kim Halsey and Arlene Krebs
      - Video (Box 119, U-matic 437_1115)
      - Video dub (Box 145, Half inch video reel 437_1961)
    - Piano performance, Museum of Modern Art, October 4-7, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0467)
    - Leaving Sutem to piano, Museum of Modern Art, October 6, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0412)
    - Compilation Tape -- Performances, October 17-23, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0423)
      Full label reads: "B. Rogue performance on 11th Street, tribute to Alphabet, playing piano - at Iris - Jackon"
    - Halloween Bowery Bash, October 28, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Edited tape shown at Broome Street, November 1, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0447)
    - Piano in studio, November 1, 1978 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0906)
    - Blondie at Palladium, November 12, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0408)
    - Car talk, November 17, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0415)
    - Piano, car talk, November 24, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0807)
      Full label reads: "Side A: 1st 2 min piano+a few words / Side B: car talk, bank, car talk and Danskin tights"
    - Piano in Morse, Carry and Arleen, December 9-26, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0428)
    - Compilation Tape -- Piano at Dord's, Amarillo, Texas, Piano and typewriter, December 11-13, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0421)
    - First chicken song, Pinball at Pendulum, Piano, December 12-28, 1978 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0817)
    - Frank Davis at Anderson Fair, December 20, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0410)
    - Compilation Tape -- Willie Nelson, Playing the Wall of C.A.M., December 20, 1978 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0424)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Willie Nelson 22- End of Will a Circle be Unbroken 23- Amazing Grace 24- Cloudy Day 25- My Lady 26- Don't no Y / Side B: Playing the wall of C.A.M. with hands, change, and chapstick"
    - A at Robert Freidus Gallery, 1978; cuid44150 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0015)
    - "AAA" Performance, Robert Freidus Gallery, 1978
      - Performance excerpts (Box 151, Half inch video reel 437_0019)
      - Video (Box 119, U-matic 437_1114)
    - Alphabet from other end and drums, 1978 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0399)
    - Alphabet with rhythm machine, 1978; cuid44151 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0011)
    - "Artists' Books" Exhibition, 1978 - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Compilation Tape -- Drumming in Parade, Piano performance at the Museum of Modern Art, 1978 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0457)
    - Piano performance, Museum of Modern Art, 1978 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1586)
    - Tonino at Mas de la Fouque, May 28, 1978; cuid44156
      - #1, cuid44157 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0009)
      - #1, cuid44158 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0007)
      - #2, cuid44159 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0008)
    - Compilation Tape -- How She Sees It by Her, Collage of Sound Performances, 1978-1981 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0317)
    - "It's A", 1978-1983; cuid44148
      - Studio 78, 1978; cuid44149 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0016)
      - Belize, April 1, 1983 (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0310)
    - New Wilderness Audiographics, 1978-1984
      - Rhythm box and vocals, March, 1978 (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0575)
      - Summer Solstice Celebration, KCR radio, June, 1983 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0866)
      - Piano, Arleen and Connie, 1984 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0782)
      - Audio, June, 1984 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0733)
      - Audio, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_2422)
      - Audio, undated (Box 109, Half inch audio reel 437_0168)
    - Tehching Hsieh Performances, 1978 - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28, Box 64, Folder 3)
    - "Mail Etc., Art" Exhibition, January, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Arleen Schloss and Blue Fox Performance, January 8, 1979 (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0292)
    - Going up to Heddas in IRT, Alphabets, January 22, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0620)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Going up to Heddas in IRT, good sub. tape / Side B: end of film Invasion of B.S. - alphabets and stops, tel. and Barbara M. speeded up video"
    - John Cage at the Whitney Museum of American Art, February 1, 1979 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0869)
    - Workshop with Michael Goldberg and Paul Tschinkel, Ernie's Video Show at Robert Freidus Gallery, February 3, 1978 - February 14, 1979 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0443)
    - Gymnast's Workshop, Lonestar Cafe, February 28 - November 30, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0611)
    - Compilation Tape -- Arlene and Kim's tapes, "It's A at MoMA," Global Village, Ear Inn, March 23, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0626)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Arlene + Kim's tapes, "It's A at MoMA," Global Village / Side B: Met old school chum at Global, leaving Global, Ernie's sound talk, (illegible) in pick up, at the Ear"
    - Tony Powers at Reno Sweeny, April 4, 1979 (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0828)
    - Compilation Tape -- Piano Layer, Meeting Risa and Andrea, John's piece in Irene's show, Ear Inn, Jack on piano, April 17-21, 1979 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0806)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Piano layer, 1+3, voice and end of 2+1+5 / Side B: Meeting Risa and Andrea, John's music piece in Irene's show, some sounds at Ear Inn, and the other night on piano with Jack"
    - Compilation Tape -- Alphabet, Richard Hayman at Franklin Furnace, Play whispering, singing, May 22, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0612)
      Full label reads: "Some alphabet and slide practice, Richard Hayman's piece at Franklin Furnace, RH (cont.) tapesounds live, some of my play whispering, singing"
    - At Bob Seltman's Space, May 30, 1979 (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0226)
    - Arleen Schloss and Young Mobile Giants -- Drums, Harmonies, Vocals, June, 1979; cuid44167 (Box 151, Super 8mm film reel 437_0017)
    - Drums, harmonica, vocals, June 8, 1979 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0401)
    - "It's A at B" Performances, June, 1979
      - Rehearsal and piano, the Ear Inn, June 10, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0686)
      - Performance preview, June 11, 1979 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1173)
      - Art Fair, Basel, Switzerland, June 17, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0687)
    - Kunst zum Hören Messeprogramm, Modern Art Galerie, Vienna, Austria, June, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - International Biennial Exhibition of Graphic and Visual Art, June 23 - July 22, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Biennal Performance, June 28, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0681)
    - Nina Richards reading, Performance by Arleen, King, and Jenny, June 29 - July 11, 1979 (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0809)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Arleen on drums, bag pipes on 5th and Nina Richards reading / Side B: first half, Arleen and King; 2nd half Arleen and King, Jenny"
    - "Audio Scene '79," Modern Art Galerie, Vienna, July - September, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - "Computer Music" Performance and conversation, Stephan Pope, July 2, 1979
      - Audio (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0610)
      - Audio (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0818)
    - Performance and radio interview, Lengenfeld, Austria, July 6-7, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0625)
      Also includes Hank Bull's performance
    - "Destroy All Blanks" and "It's A" Performances, London, July 16-18, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0630)
    - Arleen Schloss and Hank Bull Performance, Dany Keller Gallery, July 20, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0690)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Performance Side I of Arleen Schloss and Hank Bull, Munich, Germany - Dany Keller Gallery / Side B: Arleen Schloss and Hank Bull, end of performance and sounds from (illegible handwriting) Ochling"
    - "A Special Evening of Performance Art," Dany Keller Galerie, July 20, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - "Its a Scrab" Performance, Dany Keller Galerie, Munich, Germany, July 26, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0622)
    - Compilation Tape -- Ugoslave Alphabet, "Tu as des Beaux Yeux," Shot Dot Shot, A singing in the morning, September - October, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0616)
    - "Adventure A" Performance, Düsseldorf, September 7, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Compilation Tape -- Gisella's German translation, Shot Dot Shot, Airport, September 15, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0628)
    - "Sound - Medium der Bildenden Kunst," Dany Keller Galerie, September 21, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Vocals, AA Roto Gallery, November 3 - December 1, 1979 (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0494)
    - Conversation with Claire, studio check, November 10, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0680)
    - Compilation Tape -- Mussawir Gymnasts, Shot Dot, Shot Ex, November 16, 1979
      - Audio (Box 77, Audiocassette 437_0517)
      - Audio (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0525)
    - Piano performance at Ear Inn, January 12, 1978 - November 29, 1979 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0445)
    - Mania D at Tier 3, Bettina and Arleen on piano, November 18 - December 4, 1979 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0689)
    - Music at A's -- Test Pattern, December 5, 1979; FA_MSS_437_ER_3
    - Piano performance at the Ear Inn, December 5-6, 1979 (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0621)